I feel like I'm invincible now.
I hate it when people mess with you.
I'll say it.
I'll tell them...
that I hate being messed with too.
Good morning.
Morning.
Crap. Morning practice.
All right. See you later.
Okay.
You stayed overnight?
Shush!
How was it?
- Why are you asking?
- Just tell me!
- Do you wanna know?
- Come on.
- I was so happy.
- Aw, that's so great!
What was it like?
How do two guys do it?
Sui?
Huh? Wh-What?
Having trouble sleeping?
Oh, well...
Can I go over there?
Huh?
Did you have a bad dream?
This one's scented.
It will help you sleep if you want it.
Morning practice, huh?
Thanks, Harutora.
Thanks to this little guy,
I slept like a log.
"I'm glad".
"I'm always here to help".
Yeah. By the way,
where did you buy this?
"Near the train station. By the..."
Wait, this isn't right!
Is it just me?
Am I the only one this worked up?
I mean, after everything that happened!
Sui.
You're so cute.
Jeez!
Sui, what are you doing?
Meditating.
I want to get rid of my worldly desires.
Sui, what's that?
Herbs. They have a relaxing effect.
Sui.
Are you into rock music?
[Sofu High School]
That's it. I must be the one
who's gone crazy.
No way.
Seriously, all-boys schools are a desert.
Seriously, I chose the wrong school.
Must be nice for you, Sui.
You enrolled to find a boyfriend, right?
Man, impure motives, huh? That's shady.
I hate it when people mess with you.
Even if you're okay with it,
I hate it.
Actually...
I wanna go to an all-girls school.
- You're hopeless.
- Ouch.
Actually...
- What?
- What is it?
I...
No one's ever gonna like someone like me,
so I'd never find anyone here.
Yeah, we know.
- Poor Sui.
- Right?
- It's impossible.
- Why do you lack confidence?
It's not about lacking confidence.
What's wrong?
Harutora?
What are you doing here?
I was just thinking about
how hard it is to change yourself.
Huh?
I tried to tell them to stop teasing me,
but I kinda got scared,
thinking about the vibes and everything.
Is what I said weighing on you?
When I said I hate to see you getting teased,
did that make you feel pressured?
N-No, that's not it, Harutora.
I'm really happy.
Because I actually wanted to change.
Because you care about me so much,
I was able to start caring about myself too.
I love you so much, Sui.
Harutora...
Sui...
I might not be able to stop tonight.
Okay.
Sui.
Harutora.
Harutora...
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Actually...
It's too much for me.
Whoa, it's so cold!
Dude, why are you dousing yourself in water?
If only I were about your size.
Excuse me?
Sui.
Harutora.
Hey.
Wanna have dinner together tonight?
Here you go.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
Is it good?
Yes!
I'm glad.
Huh?
It's nothing.
Here, have this too.
Sui, I didn't know you cook.
Can you even call this cooking?
You okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I can't...
[4. Hygiene and preparation]
[5. Pain or discomfort is a sign to stop]
[6. There is no single way to have sex]
[7. Emotional safety is also important]
Oh, Sui. You're still here?
Yeah, I am.
Then watch this with us.
Huh, what?
I found something hilarious.
Nah, I think Sui should head back.
Hey, don't treat Sui like he's in the way.
That's not what I mean, but...
What is it? A video?
I still have time.
Are you interested? It's actually...
Don't you like BL dramas, Sui?
It's pretty sexy, honestly.
- It's crazy, right?
- How do two guys do it?
You don't know?
It's like this.
That's wild.
Come on, just go back, Sui.
Sui!
What? Hold on!
I've never seen this before. Oh, man.
Stop it.
That's just how it is.
That's the only way to do it.
That's the only way
to connect with the person you like.
You could mess up.
Or get injured.
All kinds of risks.
But they do their best so they can
be with the person they like.
So just stop making fun of it already.
Seriously, stop!
Sui!
Sorry. I happened to pass by and overheard.
I'm sorry I got scared.
Huh?
I was scared that I might hurt you.
But my feelings for you
kept growing stronger.
So...
I thought you weren't into me.
Not into you? No way!
That would never happen!
I'm sorry.
You're probably more scared than me, right?
Even just now, you faced them all alone.
I'll do my best, so...
could you give me one more chance?
Harutora...
Sui.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Are you nervous, Harutora?
Good. Me too.
Are you okay?
Y... Yeah.
Finally...
Sui.
Let me see your face.
Huh? No way.
You're so cute.
[Sofu High School]
Are you feeling okay?
Yeah.
You should take the day off.
I'm fine.
Morning.
Morning!
Good... morning.
If I win, let's go on a date.
What?
[Room Change Notice]
[Room 208: Sui Kishida
Room 103: Harutora Kurobe]
No way, I can't be
in a different room from Harutora!
Thank you for everything.
We can see each other whenever we want.
So, you like this stuff, Sui?
Get it together, Harutora!
Sorry, Harutora...
It's okay, don't worry about it.
Who was it with?